Elena Stefanovski

Economic Department of finance and credit Menagement

Goce Delcev 69 s.Kravari
Bitola, N.Macedonia

(+389) 72247320

✓ stefanovskielena@gmail.com

Personal

, I consider my self a highly motivated, decisive and reliable person. I always strive to improve and supplement my knowledge, but also to implement it trought assigned tasks and goals during the work process. My motto at work is implementing solutions, instead of pointing out problems. Over the years and the acquired experience, i have learned to work under pressure and in a dynamic environment, which is one of my great advantages and with which i belive that i will be able to contribute a lot to your company, together with my ambition, determination and skills for organization and planning.

Work Experience

2011 - 2015 Sales Assistent, DPTU DE-TA Dejan - Skopje.

Task: Customer service in the sales hall, reception and display of goods according to the company's standards, organization and arrangement of warehouse space, other work tasks related to daily functioning

2015 - 2022 **Organizational unit Menager**, DPTU DE-TA Dejan - Skopje.

Task: Organization of work duties, checks year. Organization of work, organization of quarterly sales, organization of meetings. Planning, organization and control of all processes related to the operation of the organization.

Skills and Expertise

, Highly organized, self motivated individual who can work independently as well as work effectively in a collaborative team environment, Leadership skills as well as coaching and team building. Motivate-inspire employees to support the company vision Excellent executive skills Recognized leader in business development and client relationship development, Complete understating of production, quality and cost. Skills advanced capabilities in web researching. Critical thinking.

Training

Courses and Work ethic, Introducing to communication, Active listening, Body Language, Social Seminars style, Consultative sales and mentoring

Education

2006–2011 **Graduated to the Faculty of Econonics Menagment**, *finance - credit*, International Slavic University "Gavrilo Romanovich Derzhavin" - Bitola, .

Languages

English excellent
Serbian excellent
Macedonian native speaker